Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #5, (Construction Department)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Eldorado 2,undated (Box 228, Folder 2179)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Essex,undated (Box 228, Folder 2180)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Evanston,undated (Box 228, Folder 2181)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Fairlane 1 – pane 1,1964 (Box 228, Folder 2182)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Fairlane 1-A,1963 (Box 228, Folder 2183)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Fairlane 2,undated (Box 228, Folder 2184)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Flamingo,undated (Box 228, Folder 2185)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Friendship,undated (Box 228, Folder 2186)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Fulton,undated (Box 228, Folder 2187)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Gary 1,undated (Box 228, Folder 2188)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Gary 2,undated (Box 228, Folder 2189)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Glen Cove w' quality estimates,undated (Box 228, Folder 2190)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Glen Haven 1 & 2,undated (Box 228, Folder 2191)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Glenview,undated (Box 228, Folder 2192)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Glenwood,undated (Box 228, Folder 2193)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Goodrich,undated (Box 228, Folder 2194)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Greystone 2 & 3,undated (Box 229, Folder 2195)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Grenda 1-2,undated (Box 229, Folder 2196)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Groveland 1-3,undated (Box 229, Folder 2197)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Hampton,undated (Box 229, Folder 2198)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Hartford,undated (Box 229, Folder 2199)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Hillsdale 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2200)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Holbrook 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2201)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Holbrook 2,undated (Box 229, Folder 2202)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Holland Duplex,undated (Box 229, Folder 2203)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Holmes,undated (Box 229, Folder 2204)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Hollywood 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2205)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Hummel,undated (Box 229, Folder 2206)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Jasmine, Jasmine 1 Panel – 1966, Jasmine 1 & 2 – 1964, Jasmine 2 Panel – 1966,1964-1966 (Box 229, Folder 2207)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kensington,undated (Box 229, Folder 2208)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kensington w' Anderson windows,undated (Box 229, Folder 2209)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kenton,undated (Box 229, Folder 2210)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kenwood 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2211)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kenwood 2, second floor,undated (Box 229, Folder 2212)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kimberly 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2213)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kingsbury 1 including second floor,undated (Box 229, Folder 2214)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Kingsbury 2 including second floor,undated (Box 229, Folder 2215)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Lamar,undated (Box 229, Folder 2216)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Laredo 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2217)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Laredo 2,undated (Box 229, Folder 2218)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Longwood 1,undated (Box 229, Folder 2219)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Lorain,undated (Box 229, Folder 2220)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Manchester,undated (Box 229, Folder 2221)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Manhasset 1,1957 (Box 229, Folder 2222)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Medford,undated (Box 230, Folder 2223)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Monterey 1,2 – second floor,1957 (Box 230, Folder 2224)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Monterey 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2225)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Monterey 2,undated (Box 230, Folder 2226)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Monterey 2 – second floor,undated (Box 230, Folder 2227)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Nassau,undated (Box 230, Folder 2228)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Newton 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2229)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Newton 2,undated (Box 230, Folder 2230)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Normandy 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2231)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Normandy 2,undated (Box 230, Folder 2232)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Oakland 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2233)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Oakland 2,undated (Box 230, Folder 2234)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Orlando,undated (Box 230, Folder 2235)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Palomar w' quantity estimate,undated (Box 230, Folder 2236)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Pasadena 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2237)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Pasadena 2,undated (Box 230, Folder 2238)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Parkway w' quantity estimate,undated (Box 230, Folder 2239)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Parkwood,undated (Box 230, Folder 2240)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Parkwood, 3 bedrooms, third level,undated (Box 230, Folder 2241)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Pinecrest 1,undated (Box 230, Folder 2242)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Pinecrest 2,undated (Box 231, Folder 2243)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Plaza 1,undated (Box 231, Folder 2244)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Plaza 2,undated (Box 231, Folder 2245)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Plaza 3,undated (Box 231, Folder 2246)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Plaza 3 w' Anderson windows,undated (Box 231, Folder 2247)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Plaza 4,1963-1965 (Box 231, Folder 2248)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Portage,undated (Box 231, Folder 2249)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Princeton 1,undated (Box 231, Folder 2250)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Princeton 2,undated (Box 231, Folder 2251)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Redwood w/ quantity estimates,undated (Box 231, Folder 2252)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Regency,undated (Box 231, Folder 2253)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Regency w' Anderson windows,undated (Box 231, Folder 2254)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Richmond,undated (Box 231, Folder 2255)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Ridgewood,undated (Box 231, Folder 2256)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rio Grande 2,undated (Box 231, Folder 2257)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rio Grande 4,undated (Box 231, Folder 2258)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rio Grande w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 231, Folder 2259)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Riviera 1,undated (Box 231, Folder 2260)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Riviera 2,undated (Box 231, Folder 2261)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rockwood,undated (Box 232, Folder 2262)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rosewood,undated (Box 232, Folder 2263)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rosewood w' crawl space,undated (Box 232, Folder 2264)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rosewood duplex,undated (Box 232, Folder 2265)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Rotterdam,undated (Box 232, Folder 2266)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Royton w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 232, Folder 2267)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Salem 1,undated (Box 232, Folder 2268)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Salem 2,undated (Box 232, Folder 2269)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - San Diego w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 232, Folder 2270)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Santa Fe 1,undated (Box 232, Folder 2271)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Santa Fe #3,1962, 1963, 1967 (Box 232, Folder 2272)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Saratoga w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 232, Folder 2273)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Savana #1,1979 (Box 232, Folder 2274)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Savana #2,1974 (Box 232, Folder 2275)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Savana #2,1974, 1977 (Box 232, Folder 2276)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Selma,1979 (Box 232, Folder 2277)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Shadylane #1,1956, 1961, 1963, 1971 (Box 232, Folder 2278)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Shadylane #2,1956, 1960, 1961, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 2279)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sharlear,1962, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 2280)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sharlear,1962-1964 (Box 232, Folder 2281)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Shasta #1,1980 (Box 232, Folder 2282)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Shasta #1 w' crawlspace,1981 (Box 232, Folder 2283)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sherwood #2,1966 (Box 232, Folder 2284)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sherwood #1,1965 (Box 232, Folder 2285)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sierra #1,1972 (Box 233, Folder 2286)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sierra #2,1972 (Box 233, Folder 2287)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sierra #3,1972 (Box 233, Folder 2288)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sierra #4,1972 (Box 233, Folder 2289)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sparta #1,1971, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 2290)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sparta #2,1973 (Box 233, Folder 2291)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Stratford #1,1980 (Box 233, Folder 2292)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Stratford #2,1980 (Box 233, Folder 2293)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Suburban Cottage,1981 (Box 233, Folder 2294)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sylvan #2,1957, 1961 (Box 233, Folder 2295)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sylvan #2,1962, 1964, 1965 (Box 233, Folder 2296)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sylvan #1,undated (Box 233, Folder 2297)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sylvan #3,1954, 1962 (Box 233, Folder 2298)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Sylvan #3,1969 (Box 233, Folder 2299)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Tacoma 1,undated (Box 233, Folder 2300)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Topeka 1,undated (Box 233, Folder 2301)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Topeka 2,undated (Box 233, Folder 2302)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Trenton 1,undated (Box 233, Folder 2303)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Trenton 2,undated (Box 233, Folder 2304)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Tulane,undated (Box 233, Folder 2305)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Tulsa w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 233, Folder 2306)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Ventura,undated (Box 233, Folder 2307)
  - Records, Suppliers’ Invoices - Ventura 2,undated (Box 233, Folder 2308)
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #6, (Shipping Bills)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Ventura 3,undated (Box 234, Folder 2309)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Ventura 3-A,undated (Box 234, Folder 2310)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Ventura 3-A w' two car garage,undated (Box 234, Folder 2311)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Vernon 1,undated (Box 234, Folder 2312)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Vernon 2,undated (Box 234, Folder 2313)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Vernon 3,undated (Box 234, Folder 2314)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Vinewood w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 234, Folder 2315)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Wilshire 2,undated (Box 234, Folder 2316)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Wilmington 1,undated (Box 234, Folder 2317)
  - Records, Shipping Bills -Wilshire #1,1964-1979 (Box 234, Folder 2318)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Wilshire #3,1979 (Box 234, Folder 2319)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Winslow 1,undated (Box 234, Folder 2320)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Winslow 2,undated (Box 234, Folder 2321)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Yorkshire,1974 (Box 234, Folder 2322)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Yorktown w' quantity estimates,undated (Box 234, Folder 2323)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Shipping lists – special orders (sample),undated (Box 234, Folder 2324)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Estimates – bills of materials (sample),undated (Box 234, Folder 2325)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Estimates – bills of materials (sample),undated (Box 234, Folder 2326)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Book - Poplar ‘13” Statler 3, Shipping Bills (not in alpha order),1930 (Box 235, Folder 2327)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Book - Norfolk 1 – Winston front porch,1941-1947 (Box 235, Folder 2328)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Book - Amherst – Mt. Vernon 3,1947 (Box 235, Folder 2329)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Book - Bayview 1 – Wenona 2 summer cottages,1951 (Box 235, Folder 2330)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Loose pages - Breezeways – Garages. Price bills,1951-1952 (Box 235, Folder 2331)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Envelope with pages - Westport Summer cottages, specifications,undated (Box 235, Folder 2332)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - Cottages,1960 (Box 235, Folder 2333)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - MISSING (2-11-10) - Stover Building (Aladdin office) alterations,1975 (Box 235, Folder 2334)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - MISSING (2-11-10) - Alamo-Tacoma,1964-1978 (Box 235, Folder 2335)
  - Records, Shipping Bills - MISSING (2-11-10) - House Order Shipping List,1954-1981 (Box 235, Folder 2336)
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #7, (Suppliers, Transit & Mill Sites)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Suppliers’ correspondence (incomplete),1946-1986 (Box 236, Folder 2337)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Transit correspondence,1948-1960 (Box 236, Folder 2338)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Mill site proposals,1949-1960 (Box 236, Folder 2339)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Contract mills - 1947-1960, form for contract mills - n.d.,1947-1960, undated (Box 236, Folder 2340)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Transit shipping directions & transit records,1972-1975 (Box 236, Folder 2341)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Freight register,1970, 1978-1982 (Box 236, Folder 2342)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Truck vs. rail shipping costs,1956 (Box 236, Folder 2343)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Aladdin truck delivery check list,undated (Box 236, Folder 2344)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - House weights,1966 (Box 236, Folder 2345)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Shipping schedules,1967-1977 (Box 236, Folder 2346)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Shipping diaries (bound), A. Irwin Lamb,1931, 1935, 1936, 1953 (Box 236, Folder 2347)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Shipping diaries (Lamb),1954, 1955 (Box 236, Folder 2348)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Shipping diaries (Lamb),1956 (Box 236, Folder 2349)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Purchases, 1949-1953, listed by vendor with amounts (“J.M. Horton – 1949-1960”),1949-1960 (Box 236, Folder 2350)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Purchases (3 folders),1954-1980 (Box 236, Folder 2351)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Purchases (3 folders),1954-1980 (Box 236, Folder 2352)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Purchases (3 folders),1954-1980 (Box 236, Folder 2353)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - New Method of Construction (Build-it-yourself),1962 (Box 236, Folder 2354)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Price list-Material costs,1976-1980 (Box 236, Folder 2355)
  - Records, Suppliers, Transit, Mill Sites - Kitchen layouts, Related Material,1955-1981 (Box 236, Folder 2356)
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #8, (Sovereign Family)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Homebuilders Co. Articles of Association. 1916. Correspondence re. Company, 1937, Bankbook, 1932,1916-1937 (Box 237, Folder 2357)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Deeds. N.E. corner of 11th and Washington,1916 (Box 237, Folder 2358)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Deeds 407 Washington,1916 (Box 237, Folder 2359)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Deeds. Lower Saginaw,1923-1936 (Box 237, Folder 2360)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Accountant’s Report for 1924,1924 (Box 237, Folder 2361)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Accountant’s Report for 1925,1925 (Box 237, Folder 2362)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Filings with State of Michigan,1932-1941 (Box 237, Folder 2363)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. List of documents received from National Bank of Bay City, 1932. Monthly budget for 1932,1932 (Box 237, Folder 2364)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Correspondence; estimates; rental accounts and proceedings,1932-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2365)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Agreements with National Bank of Bay City,1935-1936 (Box 237, Folder 2366)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Bay City Home Builders,1937-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2367)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Lenox Park Subdivision,1927-1939 (Box 237, Folder 2368)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Commercial Realty Company. Lenox Park Plat,1916-1928 (Box 237, Folder 2369)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Home Builders Realty Co. Lists houses for BCHB,1933-1935 (Box 237, Folder 2370)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Realty Company. Leases,1934-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2371)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Home Builders & Bay City Commercial Realty Company deeds & land contracts. Mortgage payment cards (correspondence re: sales),1916-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2372)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Home Builders & Bay City Commercial Realty Company deeds & land contracts. Mortgage payment cards (correspondence re: sales),1916-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2373)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Bay City Home Builders & Bay City Commercial Realty Company deeds & land contracts. Mortgage payment cards (correspondence re: sales),1916-1942 (Box 237, Folder 2374)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Marin lots,1882-1916 (Box 237, Folder 2375)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Mortgages, leases, budgets, receipts & disbursements, 1932-1938/ Lenox Park agreement (deed restriction), 1941 (2 copies),1932-1938, 1941 (Box 237, Folder 2376)
  - Records, Miscellaneous Other Investments/ Bay City Area Developments - Sage Land & Improvement Co,1912, 1916 (Box 237, Folder 2377)
  - Records, Correspondence - Personal (2 folders),1945-1958 (Box 238, Folder 2378)
  - Records, Correspondence - Personal (2 folders),1945-1958 (Box 238, Folder 2379)
  - Records, Correspondence - Personal business correspondence – oil,1947-1953 (Box 238, Folder 2380)
  - Records, Correspondence - Personal business correspondence – Non-oil,1949-1957 (Box 238, Folder 2381)
  - Records, Correspondence - Correspondence with universities and libraries,1956-1985 (Box 238, Folder 2382)
  - Records, Correspondence - Correspondence with newspapers,undated (Box 238, Folder 2383)
  - Records, Correspondence - Correspondence with Bay City government,1949-1987 (Box 238, Folder 2384)
  - Records, Correspondence - Contributions to political causes, 1950’s,1950-1959 (Box 238, Folder 2385)
  - Records, Correspondence - Correspondence with politicians,1952-1957 (Box 238, Folder 2386)
  - Records, Correspondence - Letters to Congress/ responses,1957 (Box 238, Folder 2387)
  - Records, Correspondence - Lobby correspondence,1958-1963 (Box 238, Folder 2388)
  - Records, Correspondence - Correspondence with Clarks,1949-1958 (Box 238, Folder 2389)
  - Records, Correspondence - Rachel Sovereign Home correspondence,undated (Box 238, Folder 2390)
  - Records, Correspondence - Charitable donations,1953-1958 (Box 238, Folder 2391)
  - Records, Correspondence - Obituary, Mrs. William J. Sovereign, January 4, 1944,1944 (Box 238, Folder 2392)
  - Records, Correspondence - J. Sovereign ciphering book,1978 (Box 238, Folder 2393)
  - Records, Correspondence - Sovereign, Otto E. Fifty Million Dollars on a Shoestring (and Fifty years of Fun). N.P.: By the author (2 copies),1951 (Box 238, Folder 2394)
  - Records, Correspondence - Sovereign, Otto E. Fifty Million Dollars on a Shoestring (and Fifty years of Fun). N.P.: By the author (2 copies),1951 (Box 238, Folder 2395)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Register (Bay City Boating and Fishing Club),1895-1898 (Box 239, Folder 2399)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Register (?),1899-1904 (Box 239, Folder 2398)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Membership List, Boat List, and Financial Records,1939 (Box 239, Folder 2397)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Meeting Minutes (primarily annual meeting),1920-1942 (Box 239, Folder 2401)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Financial Records,1911-1927 (Box 239, Folder 2400)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Financial Records,1939-1943 (Box 239, Folder 2402)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - The Masthead (miscellaneous issues),1938-1944 (Box 239, Folder 2403)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Correspondence, re original 6 class boats,1944 (Box 239, Folder 2404)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Club (and predecessor organization) Records - Bay City Yacht Club golden anniversary program, (OES & WJS members),1944 (Box 239, Folder 2396)
  - Records, Sally Sovereign Miscellaneous Photos,undated (Box 240, Folder 2406)
  - Records, Sally Sovereign Miscellaneous Photos,undated (Box 240, Folder 2407)
  - Records, Sally Sovereign Miscellaneous Photos,undated (Box 240, Folder 2408)
  - Records, Jeanette Lempke Newspaper Clippings re. Aviation – loose copies of newspaper articles,undated (Box 240, Folder 2405)
  - Records, Bay City Yacht Clum Boat (1919-1937) and Visitor (1906-1911) Registers,1906-1937 (Box 241, Folder 2409)
  - Records, Litigation: William F. Sovereign vs. Mary K. Sovereign and related proceedings (Consists of published material or material part of the court records) - Booklet: State of Michigan in the Supreme Court – Brief for Plaintiff-Appellant, File No. 17542, File No. 18465, Cal No. 49664,1953-1961 (Box 242, Folder 2410)
  - Records, Litigation: William F. Sovereign vs. Mary K. Sovereign and related proceedings (Consists of published material or material part of the court records) - Decree of Divorce,1961 (Box 242, Folder 2411)
  - Records, Litigation: William F. Sovereign vs. Mary K. Sovereign and related proceedings (Consists of published material or material part of the court records) - Book: State of Michigan in Supreme Court, Sovereign v. Sovereign, Record of Appeal Vol. 1,1953-1961 (Box 242, Folder 2412)